

# TASNUVA SYED

#### **PROFILE**

A creative, skilled content writer with a vast experience of writing articles, blogs, compositions for various projects. Has a knack for engaging the audience emotionally with an unique story telling style and accurate research on each article.

#### CONTACT

+880 1848077997

🔽 tasnuva.dd17@gmail.com

tasnuvasyed.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/tasnuvasyed17

facebook.com/tasnuvasyed17

Room #1010, Shamshun nahar Hall, University of Dhaka

### SKILLS

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Excel

Abode Illustrator

Wordpress

Python

### **EDUCATION**

University of Dhaka

JAN 2017 - PRESENT

BSS, Department of Economics 4th Year (7th Semester)

Chittagong College

JUL 2014 - AUG 2016

HSC, Science, GPA 5.00

Dr. Khastagir Govt. Girls' HIgh School, Chittagong

JAN 2008 - MAY 2014

SSC, Science, GPA 5.00

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

**Best Writer Award** 

NOV 2018

Robi 10 Minute School

**Best Debater** 

NOV 2012

Drishty Ctg School of Debate

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

**Blog Intern** 

APR 2018 -NOV 2018

Robi 10 Minute School

**Content Writing Intern** 

AUG 2020 - OCT2020

**Interactive Cares**